ANDRÉS ALEXANDRO TAPIA

SUMMARY

Full stack software developer from Ecuador, best graduated Mechatronics engineer with experience in languages and frameworks like: JavaScript (React - NextJs, AngularJs, Angular 9, Express, Handlebars), Python (Flask, Django, Jinja), CSS (Bootstrap, Sass), C++, C#, Java, HTML, VBScript, MQL4 – MQL5, Ladder, LabVIEW, MATLAB. And designing, creating and managing databases in MongoDB, Redis, MySQL, Firebase - Firestore and Realtime database. Experience using and developing in Microsoft, AWS, Google and other paid and Open-Source technologies (Git, Postman, Celery, RabbitMQ, Netlify, Vercel, Twilio, DialogFlow, Jira, Slack, HubSpot, Zapier, Hubstaff, Bitbucket).

Email: alexandrotapiaflores@gmail.com

Phone: +593998775709

EDUCATION

ESPE (Escuela Superior Politécnica del Ejército)

• Best graduated Mechatronics Engineer

July - 2019

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

- Programming languages: Javascript,
 Python, HTML, CSS, C#, C++, VBScript,
 Ladder (PLC), MQL4, MQL5, Java, MATLAB.
- Databases: MongoDB, Redis, MySQL,
 Firebase Firestore, Firebase Real time database.
- Frameworks: Django, Flask, Express. NextJs
- DevOps: Linode, DigitalOcean, Nginx, Certbot, PM2, Docker, Ionos, Freenom, Hostinger, Vagrant, Git, Github, Bitbucket.
- Other software used: Slack, Jira, HubSpot, Zapier, Hubstaff, Twilio.
- Spanish: Native, English: Fluent.
- Other skills: CAD-CAM-CAE, AutoCAD,

SOLIDWORKS.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ten Tech Feb 2013 - Jul 2018

Software developer, specialist in mechatronics.

- Ladder
- C++
- Java
- Python
- MATLAB
- WordPress

ESPE Sep 2018 – Dic 2018

Leader software developer of a team focused on the rehabilitation of kids with autism (Social robots).

- LabVIEW
- C++
- C#
- VBScript

Localhost (entrepreneurship)

Feb 2019 - Current

CEO and developer of the company.

- PMP
- Leadership

Kings Of Binary Jan 2020 - Current

Full stack developer, specialist in Backend and DevOps.

- NodeJs
- Flask
- Firebase
- Linode
- Nginx
- Certbot
- Wordpress
- MQL4 MQL5

Devsu Oct 2020 - Current

Full stack developer, specialist in Backend and DevOps.

- AngularJS
- Angular 9
- Django
- Celery
- RabbitMQ
- AWS (IAM, EC2, ROUTE53, S3, RDS)
- Firebase (auth, real-time database, firestore, firebase hosting)